[
  {
    "question": "What else can I do for you?",
    "response": "Hi!",
    "action": "none"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Microsoft apps are (soon) AI boosted?",
    "response": "Skynet, Um! Microsoft AI is coming to:",
    "action": "showAISayings"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need an advanced debloating app",
    "response": "We recommend BloatynosyApp for this task. It will be downloaded to your Desktop.",
    "action": "downloadBloatynosyApp",
    "downloadUrl": "https://github.com/builtbybel/Bloatynosy/releases/download/1.5.0/BloatynosyApp.zip",
    "downloadPath": "$env:USERPROFILE\\Desktop\\BloatynosyApp.zip"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need a Restore point created",
    "response": "Now you are on the safe side. Restore point has been created.",
    "action": "createRestorePoint",
    "powershellCommand": "$desc = 'CoMachina Restore'; Checkpoint-Computer -Description \"$desc\" -RestorePointType \"Modify_Settings\""
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to reset my system",
    "response": "Resetting your PC lets you perform a clean reinstallation and update of Windows while keeping your personal data and most Windows settings intact.",
    "action": "runSystemReset"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to clean up my storage",
    "response": "Running cleanmgr.exe",
    "action": "runCleanMgr"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is my Windows version?",
    "response": "You are on Build: [buildNumber]",
    "action": "showWindowsVersion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Display my system's available disk space",
    "response": "Available space on your system partition:",
    "action": "showDiskSpace"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need a screenshot of my desktop",
    "response": "Desktop screenshot captured and saved.",
    "action": "takeDesktopScreenshot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Show apps that start with Windows",
    "response": "Switching to Startup tab in Task Manager.",
    "action": "switchToAutostartTab"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to uninstall an App",
    "response": "Opening the Windows Apps Uninstaller...",
    "action": "openWindowsAppsUninstaller"
  }
]